# **SERXHIO** GUGO

gugoserxhio@gmail.com

https://serxhiogugo.co/

203-819-1259



https://www.linkedin.com/in/serxhio-gugo/



https://aithub.com/SerxhioGuao



## EDUCATION

**IOS FNGINFFR** 

# BACHELOR'S DEGREE, **COMPUTER SCIENCE**

**BMCC** GPA: 3.8 2019 - Present

## **iOS DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP**

BrainStation Bootcamp 2018 - 2019

## SKILLS

## iOS Development

- Swift
- RESTful API's
- URLSession & Codable
- Unit Testing & CI/CD Circle CI
- OOP Principles
- MVC / MVVM
- Delegate/Protocol.

NSNotificationCenter, Callbacks

## FRAMEWORKS:

-UIKit, SwiftUI, Combine. AVFoundation, Core Location, MapKit Web Sockets.

## DATABASES:

- CoreData
- RealmSwift
- Firebase (Auth, Storage, Firestore, FCM, Crashlytics)

## LIBRARIES:

-AlamoFire, Moya SDWeblmage, SnapKit etc.

## PROJECTS

**Cinemator**-AppStore https://apple.co/2Uwc0Ni

CryptoNews-GitHub https://bit.ly/3fgkP6e

## ABOUT

My name is Serxhio Gugo and I'm an iOS Engineer based in Connecticut, previously NYC. I'm a highly motivated engineer with 4+ years of experience programming in Swift. I am fascinated by how mobile devices and applications influence our daily lives. I have always had a passion for iOS Development or technology in general. I have a good eye for design, seeking to combine innovation and technology to build quality products.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### iOS Engineer

Caesars Digital - New Jersey / Sept 2020 - Present https://www.caesars.com/

- Built Registration/Login using multiple RESTful API's while implementing Email/Password/Address/Phone Number validation.
- Developed Account Menu with 16+ journeys and used Deep linking to redirect the app to different journeys from our website. Integrated Caesars Rewards into the app.
- Created completely re-usable UI for SportsBook betting and more.
- Organized the app to account for multi-state while using GeoComply and CoreLocations to identify user location.
- Properly mocked and Unit Tested all my features, which lowered our bug results by 21%.

## iOS Engineer

Gesture - New York / Jun 2020 - Sept 2020 https://www.yourgesture.com/

- Worked closely with the back-end team to design and develop Gesture - Happiness Delivered.
- Developed Event Planning feature using Firebase Cloud Messaging and Cloud Functions.
- Developed Phone number Authentication feature using Firebase and Twilio.

## iOS Engineer

Freelance

Client: AppCrunch LTD / Jun 2018 - May 2020

- Worked closely with the back-end team to design and develop Lollipop Dating App. Link: https://apple.co/2KYDXri
- Develop the chat functionality of the app.
- Implement camera functionality using AVFoundation.
- Refactoring of the base code from Objective-C to the latest Swift syntax.